漫威影業出品
根據布萊恩·邁克爾·班迪斯和邁克爾·蓋多斯
所創作的漫威作品而改編
傑西卡
瓊斯
第一季  第十三集 本季終
疼痛總是忽如其來
Pain is always a surprise.
救命  來人啊  救命
Help! Somebody, please. Please help!
我試圖避過地雷
I try to avoid landmines.
-怎麼回事  -他撞到頭了
- What happened? - He hit his head.
逃避關心
Avoid caring.
我甚至能預見到它的到來
I can even see it coming.
但直到疼痛襲來前  你都不知道那是什麼感覺
But until it hits, you have no idea what pain is.
-什麼情況  -頭部受到撞擊且昏迷
- What do we got? - A head injury with LOC.
疑似鈍器擊傷
Possible blunt force trauma.
-沒有知覺  -沒有瘀傷或傷口
- Unresponsive. - No bruising, lacerations.
我告訴你了  他被擊暈了
I'm telling you, he got knocked out.
火藥殘余  你看見他中槍了嗎
Gunpowder? Did you see him get shot?
我只看到他昏迷
I saw him unconscious.
-快做點什麼  -做斷層掃描
- Are you gonna do something? - Let's get a CT scan.
-你去接待處等著吧  -不
- You can wait in the reception area. - No.
聽著  你做了件好事
Hey, you did a good thing.
如果他能活下來  都是因為你
If he survives, it's because of you.
腦水腫並伴有占位效應
Cerebral edema with mass effect.
準備顱內壓導管
Prep for an intracerebral pressure catheter,
注射100克甘露醇來消腫
100 grams of mannitol to bring the swelling down.
操
Oh, shit.
針有問題
Something's weird with the needle.
抱歉
Sorry.
不是吧
Come on!
-你他媽在幹什麼  -不是我
- What the hell are you doing? - It's not me.
-你別幹了  -不
- You're done. - No.
是他的問題  或者是這些針
It's him! Or these needles!
我需要個知道自己在幹什麼的護士
I need a damn nurse who knows what they're doing.
-你是在浪費時間  -我可以的
- You're wasting time! - I got this.
血壓上升
Blood pressure's climbing.
不能等了
He can't wait.
做非侵入性手術
No, do something non-invasive.
帶她出去
Remove her, please.
血壓180/110
180 over 110.
-女士  請你  -放開我
- Ma'am, I'm gonna have you-- - Get off me.
好吧
Okay.
他是  他們中的一個
He's, uh... one of those.
把大外科主任和主席醫生找來
I need the Head of Surgery, and find the Chief of Staff.
美國醫院或醫療系統內醫生組織選舉出的主席
我要跟他們商量商量
I need a consult.
抱歉  先生  你不能進來
Uh, I'm sorry, sir. I can't let you in there.
請你幫幫他
Please help him.
我不是醫生  而且我也不覺得醫生能幫他
I'm not a doctor. I don't think any doctor can fix this.
那我得把他帶走
Then I need to get him out of here.
如果警察是來找他的  我必須上報
You know, if those cops are here for him, I need to report this.
警察搞錯了  他是好人
The cops have it wrong. He is a good man.
他只是被一個邪惡的混蛋給利用了
He just got used by an evil prick.
是這個邪惡的混蛋對他腦袋開槍的嗎
This evil prick the one who put a shotgun to his head?
不  槍是我開的  我別無選擇
No, that was me, and I didn't have a choice.
-好吧  我不管了  -我有選擇
- Okay, I'm done. - I did have a choice...
我選擇生存
and I chose to survive.
這個時候移動他可能會害死他
You know, moving him might kill him.
把他留在這裡會暴露他
Leaving him here will expose him.
聽著  我知道你很怕我們
Look, I know that we scare you,
你從沒見過我們這種人
and you've never seen anything like us,
但這是個好人
but this is a good man.
-那你呢  -我是個混蛋
- And you? - I'm an asshole.
要麼幫我要麼滾開
But help me or get out of my way.
我不害怕  我也不是第一次見到你這種人
You don't scare me, and you're not my first.
五樓的天橋
The fifth floor bridge
通到街對面的停車場
goes to a parking structure across the street.
我有車
I have a car.
你要帶他去哪裡
Where are you taking him?
離開這裡  我只想到這裡
Out of here. That's as far as I got.
你不能帶他去我那裡
Well, you're not taking him to my place.
這種事發生過  害我被房東趕出來了
Been there, done that, lost my lease.
我家很近
My apartment's close.
那裡一團糟  不過他也知道
It's a disaster, but he already knows that.
他會死嗎
Is he gonna die?
我不知道
I don't know.
給他冰敷  餵他服藥紓解腫脹
You can ice him, use oral meds to reduce his swelling.
不過結果很難預料
But it's... it's a crapshoot.
別這樣了  這樣幫不了他
Might as well stop that right now. It won't do him any good.
-怎樣  -內疚讓人做蠢事
- Stop what? - Guilt makes people do stupid shit.
我沒感到內疚
I'm not guilty.
這不是我的錯
It's not my fault.
我討厭這一點
See, I hate that.
我希望所有事都是因為我  不論好壞
I want everything to be my fault. Good or bad.
至少說明我還有所掌控
Means I have some control.
-但你沒有  -很顯然
- You don't. - Obviously.
但這讓我繼續幻想著我可以改變他人
But it keeps me dreaming I can change things for people.
這就是例子
Case in point.
一切盡在你掌控之中
You're in total control.
這一切都是你的錯  我怪你
You're responsible for all of this and I blame you.
別得寸進尺了
Don't push it.
以防萬一
Just in case.
傑西卡·瓊斯
Jessica Jones?
-怎麼了  -你是傑西卡·瓊斯
- Why? - Are you Jessica Jones?
艾麗  我們見過  我是急診的克萊爾
Ellie, we've met. I'm Claire, down in Emergency.
你的電話  你必須接
This call is for you. You have to take it.
你能把他送去這個地址嗎
Will you take him to this address?
假名調查事務所
傑西卡·瓊斯
幹什麼
What?
別這樣  至少裝作吃驚的樣子
Oh, come on, be a little surprised it's me.
你在這一片唯一的醫院裡找到了我
You found me at the only hospital in the neighborhood.
真讓人吃驚
Big surprise.
你的能力範圍又擴大了
You've expanded your reach.
但沒影響到我
But not to me.
就知道你會救自己  男朋友去死好了
Should have known you'd save your own skin, boyfriend be damned.
還是一樣自私
Selfish as ever.
很顯然  愛過失去過並沒有多好
Clearly, it's not better to have loved and lost.
-你肯定很後悔遇到盧克  -安保中心在哪裡
- I'm sure you regret having ever met Luke. - Where's your security center?
東翼  二樓
Uh, east wing, second floor.
我就很後悔遇到你
I certainly regret meeting you.
太好了  我們終於有地方一樣了
Oh, good, then we finally have something in common.
後悔
Regret.
還有憎恨  別忘了這一點
And hatred. Let's not forget about that one.
對你來說  幸運的是  我們已經在醫院了
Fortunately, for you, we're already at a hospital,
等我把你舌頭扯下來之後就醫會很方便
so when I rip your tongue from your skull, it'll be a short trip.
你真是個小畜生  是不是
You really are a little anal crumpet, aren't you?
罵人  這可不是你的風格
Name calling, that's not really your style.
我沒死讓你很生氣嗎
Oh, no, are you upset with me for not dying?
我妨礙到你的邪惡計劃了嗎
Did I foil your evil plan?
邪惡  得了  別這麼輕描淡寫
"Evil"? Come on, how reductive.
我很邪惡是不是意味著你是好人
I suppose "Me, evil" means "You, good." bullshit.
確實殺人之前我從來沒多想過
I mean, it's true that I've never given a second thought
但是我並不覺得那有什麼樂趣
to anyone that I've let die, but I take no pleasure in it...
真正邪惡之人一定會這樣
like a truly evil man would.
我只是鏟除公害而已
I'm merely... removing nuisances.
更像是公共服務
Public service, really.
而你
But you...
我相信這是第一次
I believe for the first time,
我會很高興的看著你死亡
I will rather enjoy watching you die.
我也有同感
The feeling's mutual.
傑西卡·瓊斯
Jessica Jones!
將魚皮剝掉  然後
...simply removes the fish from the skin and at that point...
全體人員請注意  訪客  抱怨的人
Paging all personnel, visitors, the whining,
傷員和將死之人
the wounded and dying.
不是吧
Oh, hell, no.
一種危險的病毒正在醫院大樓內傳播
A dangerous virus has been spread throughout this building.
請前往最近的電視收看緊急指示
For emergency instructions, turn to your closest video screen.
市綜合醫院
這是傑西卡·瓊斯
This is Jessica Jones.
他不能控制醫院裡的所有人
He can't control everyone in the hospital.
她是首例患者
She is patient zero.
她身上的病毒將毀滅你們所有人
Her poison will destroy you all,
除非你們先找到她並殺了她
unless you find and kill her first.
現在開始
Now.
也許他能
Unless he can.
別動  不然打斷你的屁股
Stay, you'll break a hip.
去其他房間找找  她不在這裡
Search the other ones! She's not in here.
安全  去其他房間找找
All clear. Check the other one.
還沒找到她
We haven't found her yet!
她肯定在什麼地方
She's gotta be here somewhere.
去東走廊找找
Go down the east hallway.
等不及要殺掉這個傑西卡·瓊斯了  是嗎
Can't wait to kill this Jessica Jones, huh?
得先找到她
Have to find her first.
這裡安全  去走廊
No, this is clear. Let's take this hallway.
傑西卡·瓊斯
Jessica Jones!
是傑西卡
It's Jessica!
混蛋
God damn it!
你女朋友還真邋遢
Your girlfriend's a slob.
你有超能力
Man, you got powers.
是時候用它了
Now is the time to use 'em.
操
Oh, shit!
不  不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
好
Okay.
-你在幹什麼  -按住他的頭
- What the hell are you doing? - Hold his head still!
我要抽他的腦脊髓液
I gotta drain the cerebral-spinal fluid.
你無法劃破他的皮膚
He has unbreakable skin.
-我沒準備穿透他的皮膚  -你當真嗎
- I'm not going through his skin. - Are you serious?
上帝啊
Jesus!
我要將針管沿著視神經扎進去
I have to slide the needle along the optic nerve,
所以我要你緊緊按住他
so I need you to hold him very still.
-你能做到嗎  -你能做到嗎
- Can you do that? - Can you do that?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
好了
Okay.
我要扎了
I'm going in.
我要扎進頭蓋骨
I have to get into the cranium.
上帝啊
Ah, Jesus.
-你堅持不住他就死定了  -我沒問題
- You puke, he's done! - I'm good.
扎進去了
I'm in.
他會沒事嗎
Is he gonna be all right?
得等他醒來才知道
Won't know till he wakes up.
我要喝一杯  你要嗎
I need a drink. You want a drink?
我要喝一杯
I'm having a drink.
現在是凌晨五點
It's 5 in the morning.
沒錯
Exactly.
你知道盧克的電話在哪裡嗎
Do you know where Luke's phone is?
知道
Yeah.
他身上只有一部電話  沒有任何來電
It was the only thing on him. He hasn't gotten any calls.
繼續給他冰敷
Just keep him iced.
現在能做的只有等了
At this point, it's just a waiting game.
我得回醫院去
I have to get back to the hospital.
你受傷了嗎
Did you get cut?
給我看看
I suppose I gotta look at that.
我得走了  不過得先找到地方
I have to go. Just need to find out where.
你得走了
You have to go?
床上有個陷入昏迷的大塊頭男人你卻要走
With a large unconscious man in your bed?
他不會是最後一個
He won't be the last...
基爾格雷夫傷害的人
person hurt by Killgrave.
是你所說的邪惡的混蛋
The so-called "Evil prick"?
手機沒電了
Stupid phone is dead.
好吧
All right, well...
如果你腿上傷口感染了  那你哪裡都去不了
if your leg gets infected, you're not going anywhere.
脫褲子吧
Take off your pants.
我喜歡對方更浪漫點
I usually like a little more romancing.
誰不是呢
Don't we all?
是基爾格雷夫幹的嗎
So, did Killgrave do that to you?
不  他不會自己下手
No, he doesn't do his own dirty work.
-他控制大腦  -你在開玩笑吧
- He controls minds. - You're joking.
如果你覺得無法穿透的皮膚
It's fine by me if unbreakable
已經是底限了  我也能接受
skin is where you wanna draw the line.
估計是因為
Guess it's just harder to believe
很難相信有人會叫自己基爾格雷夫吧
someone would call himself... "Killgrave."
乾脆叫白痴算了
I mean, why not just "Snuffcarcass"?
傷口齊整  很深
Clean and deep.
但是應該不用縫合
But I think we can get away without stitches.
你要怎麼阻止能控制大腦的人
So, how do you stop a mind-controller?
我得先找到他
I have to find him first.
基爾格雷夫控制了盧克
Killgrave had control of Luke.
他讓他持續匯報我的行蹤
He had him calling in with updates on me.
如果可以追蹤盧克撥打的號碼
So, if I can trace the number that Luke was calling,
也許能幫我找到基爾格雷夫的藏身之所
it might get me closer to where Killgrave is holed up.
為什麼要你去面對他
And what makes you the one who has to face him?
霉運吧
Crap-ass luck.
我曾
I had...
我有個朋友與你和盧克很像
have a friend like you and Luke.
失血加昏迷
Bleeding and unconscious?
大多數時候確實如此
Yeah, actually, more often than not.
他與壞人為敵
He makes life hard for bad guys.
他怎麼知道自己是好人
How's he so sure he's the good guy?
他不知道
He isn't.
他質疑自己的每一步舉動
He questions every move he makes...
和每一個想法
every thought he has.
我猜你也是一樣
Just like I'm guessing you do.
我可以聯繫他  他也許能幫上忙
I could reach out to him. He might help.
我不能冒險再讓其他人受到控制了
I can't risk another person getting controlled.
這一點我很確定
It's the only thing I don't question.
我得自己殺了他
I have to kill him on my own.
我沒能攔下她  都是你的錯  爸爸
I couldn't stop her. And it's your bloody fault, Dad!
你現在比以前更為強大
You're more powerful than ever.
如果你多給我一點呢  全都給我
What would happen if you gave me the lot? All of it?
一整瓶
A whole dram?
我不知道
I don't know.
好好猜猜
Well, make an educated guess.
百分之四十的機率能讓你變得更強
40% chance it makes you stronger.
百分之六十的機率會殺了你
60% it kills you.
我知道我想要什麼
I know which one I want.
你呢  爸爸  你想要什麼
What about you, Dad? Which do you want?
我想讓它殺了你
I want it to kill you.
想想  我可是他親兒子
His own son, imagine.
話說回來  我也有同樣的想法
For what it's worth, I feel the same way.
全都給我
Give me everything you've got.
也許我能強到可以再次控制她
Maybe I'll get strong enough to control her again.
上帝啊
God.
上帝啊  我願意不惜一切代價再看一眼
Dear God, I would do anything to see the look on her face
當她發現自己孑然無助時的表情
when she realizes she's helpless.
我要讓她想要我
I'd make her want me.
然後拒絕她
Then reject her.
一次又一次的摧毀她  直到她想去死
Devastate her over and over and over until she wants to die.
但是我也不會讓她死的
No, I won't give her that, either.
她會像那些渴死或者餓死的人一樣逐漸枯萎
She'd wither away like someone dying of thirst or starvation.
困在為她專門設計的地獄之中
Be a certain ring of hell, designed specially for her.
也許我會殺了她
Or maybe I'll just kill her.
開始吧  阿爾伯特
Shall we, Albert?
開始實驗吧
Let the experiment begin.
我想過你
I thought about you.
我知道這不會實現
I mean, I knew it would never happen.
但我禁不住想像我們
But I couldn't help... picturing us.
出去約會
Like, on an actual date.
打保齡球
Bowling.
做正常人做的事
Normal shit.
你是第一個讓我想像未來的人
You're the first person I ever pictured a future with.
你也是第一個我開槍打中腦袋的人
You're also the first person I ever shot in the head.
如果你
If you--
等你醒來
When you wake up...
我不會再在你身邊打擾你的生活了
I'm not gonna be around to screw up your life anymore.
恐怕是因為我已經死了
Probably because I'll be dead.
也許基爾格雷夫也死了
But maybe Killgrave will be dead, too.
有電了
You got power!
你的手機
Your phone.
也許能幫我找到基爾格雷夫
Might get me to Killgrave.
你毫無知覺卻仍在幫我
You're freaking unconscious and you're helping me.
我本來會喜歡那種未來的
I would have liked that future.
會有點刺疼
This could sting.
那不是什麼刺疼  爸爸  這像是被烙鐵燙
It doesn't sting, Dad, it burns like a poxy branding iron.
搜索  賈斯丁·波頓
有發現嗎
Find something?
賈斯丁·波頓
Justin Boden.
搜索  賈斯丁·波頓
那是誰
Who's he?
避險基金經紀人  住在豪華地段
Hedge fund broker. Fancy address.
基爾格雷夫用他的手機給盧克打電話
Killgrave used his phone to call Luke.
他可以就這麼拿其他人的手機用嗎
He can just take someone's phone like that?
只拿手機就算是幸運的了
They're lucky if that's all he takes.
克萊爾  我需要你幫個忙
Claire, I need a favor.
-再幫個忙  -我得去上班了
- Another favor. - I have to get to work.
我知道
I know.
你予人幫助
You help people.
你就是這樣的人
That's who you are.
你讓其他人看起來像是自私的混蛋
And you make the rest of us look like selfish pricks.
這是讚揚還是
Is that a compliment or--
醫院有其他人可以幫助他人
There are other nurses at the hospital who can help.
但能幫盧克的只有一個
There's only one that can help Luke.
我不想他醒來時獨自一人
I just don't want him to wake up alone,
不知道發生了什麼
not knowing what's happening.
我也不知道發生了什麼
I don't even know what's happening.
我知道這要求很過分  你並不認識我  但
It's asking a lot, and you don't know me, but...
我了解你
Sure I do.
我畢竟看你脫過褲子
I've seen you with your pants down.
你能來接我下嗎
Can you pick me up?
謝謝  崔西  我在大樓外面等你
Thanks, Trish. I'll be waiting outside.
我上去就未必能下來了
I go up there, I might not come back.
所以我要知道
So I want you to tell me
你那天過來想跟我說什麼
what you came over the other day to tell me.
你在搞什麼  遺言嗎
What is this, last words?
我想知道
I want to know.
為辛普森的藥物實驗提供資金的IGH私人研究機構
The IGH private research group that funded Simpson's drug trials?
我查出點線索表明該機構
I might've found something
也許和你身上的超能力有關係
that connects it to you and how you got your powers.
我早就放棄尋找答案了
I gave up looking for answers a long time ago.
我沒有
I didn't.
這也許確有問題  也許什麼事都沒
Look, it might be something, it might lead to nothing.
-你走過許多死胡同  -我知道
- There have been a lot of dead ends. - I know.
但你總是邁步跨過
But you just kept pushing past them.
好像你有鐵打的意志
It's like you have this iron will.
為我堅強下去  好嗎
Hold on to it for me, will you?
-崔西  別這樣  -我要和你一起去
- Trish, don't! - I'm finishing this with you.
我是想說  等我呼叫支援
I was gonna say, wait until I call for backup.
團隊合作  不是嗎  我在哪裡聽說過
Teamwork, right? I read about that somewhere.
好吧  我等著  給我簡訊
Okay, I'll wait here. Just... text me.
你不知道我是不是被控制了
You won't know if I'm a minion of evil.
我們需要個暗號
Well, we need a signal.
你絕對不會說的話  比如
Something you would never say, like...
沙丁魚  或者醃菜汁
"Sardines" Or "Pickle juice."
你說暗號  我就知道你還是你
You say it, you're still you.
我絕對不會說的話
Something I never say.
比如我愛你
Like, "I love you."
那也行
That'll do.
基爾格雷夫在哪裡
Hey, where's Killgrave?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
住手
Stop!
我得把爸爸從地球上抹掉
I... I have to remove Dad from the face of the Earth.
不  你不用這麼做  住手吧  沒事了
No, you don't. Stop, it's okay.
然後我們得自殺
But then we have to kill ourselves!
上帝啊
Oh, God.
他更強了
He's stronger.
別聽他說話  別看他
Don't listen. Don't look at him.
他會讓你殺人的
He'll make you kill.
他去哪裡了
Where did he go?
阿爾伯特
Albert.
傑西卡
樓頂  我愛你
我今天來不了  雪莉
I can't come in, Shirley.
我有點急事要辦
I have a personal emergency.
我知道人手不夠  但是
I know we're short, but...
好吧
Okay.
我一脫身就過來
I'll come when I can.
你是誰
Who are you?
-你是誰  -鄰居
- Who are you? - Neighbor.
護士
Nurse.
操  傑西卡受傷了嗎
Oh, shit. Is Jessica hurt?
就我所知  她安然無恙
She's all right, far as I know.
她在哪裡
Where is she?
傑西
Jess?
我靠
Oh, God damn.
-你認識他  -對  盧克  他怎麼了
- You know him? - Yeah, Luke. What happened to him?
我不知道
I don't know.
我也不想知道
Not sure I want to.
所以你是個特殊護士嗎
So, are... you some kind of special nurse?
特殊  意思是
"Special"? As in...
不  我一點都不特殊
Nope, I'm not special.
只是一直遇到特殊之人
I just keep running into special.
我也是
Ah, you and me both.
這是好事嗎
Is it a good thing?
什麼都忘不掉
Can't change what we know.
我也懷念一無所知的感覺
Yeah, I miss ignorance, too.
不久前我還在
Wasn't that long ago I was...
爭取拿到社會福利的學位
trying to get my degree in social work.
想要幫助他人
Wanted to help people?
現在也是一樣
I still do.
不需要超能力也能做到
don't need powers to be of use.
我也不想要超能力
I don't want powers.
我的意思是
I mean, I do not want to
我也不想成為超能力的受害者  但是
be on the receiving end of them either, but...
說不清  我太喜歡人了
I don't know, I just-- I like people too much.
盧克  傑西卡
Luke, Jessica,
不管從什麼角度來看  他們都是獨立的個體
just by necessity, by definition, they're separate.
其實對他們彼此來說也是一樣
Even from each other.
也許這就是我們能給他們的東西
Maybe that's what they need most from us.
人與人之間的聯繫
Connection.
那我們算什麼  跟班
What does that make us? Sidekicks?
我才不是什麼跟班
Oh, I'm no one's sidekick.
我看得出來
I can see that.
傑西卡就是那種人  你知道嗎
Jessica's got it in her, you know?
也許她自己從未發現  但她就是
And she may well never find it, but it is in there.
酒鬼
An alcoholic?
英雄
A hero.
那一行可不好幹
Tough business.
你也是一樣
So is yours.
你休息會兒吧  我來看著他
Why don't you take a break for a while? I'll watch him.
謝了
Thanks.
你不能控制大腦吧
You're not a... mind-controller, right?
基爾格雷夫  邪惡的混蛋
Killgrave. Evil prick.
那就好
Okay.
我去沙發上躺會兒
I'll be on the couch.
如果你倒下了  我們就都完了
Man, if you got taken down, we are all in the shit.
上帝啊
Christ.
傑瑞·霍加斯
Jeri Hogarth.
生物材料  胚胎組織  霍普·施洛曼
"Biological material, fetal tissue, Hope Shlottman.
J·霍加斯提交檢測
Submitted to testing by J. Hogarth."
基爾格雷夫逼我告訴他在哪裡的  反正也沒用
Killgrave made me tell him where it was. It's useless anyway.
不  那讓他更強了
No, it made him stronger.
我不知道還要怎麼樣才能彌補我的過錯
I don't know what else I can do to pay for my mistakes.
我為此流過血  失去了我在乎的一切
I have bled for them, I have lost everything that I care about.
帕姆正面臨著謀殺指控  她不願意見我
Pam is facing murder charges, and she won't see me,
而我的合伙人逼我退出
and my partners are forcing me out.
別聽他們的
Don't let them.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
-和他們抗爭  -為什麼
- Fight them. - Why?
你就是你
Because you are who you are.
穿著昂貴西裝的一坨屎
A sack of dark oozing shit in an expensive suit.
傑西卡
Jessica...
所以你才是這個城市裡最好的律師
Which makes you the best shark in town,
而你要去免費代理賈斯丁·波頓
and you're gonna represent Justin Boden pro bono.
-誰  -基爾格雷夫的另一個受害者
- Who? - Another one of Killgrave's victims.
他會被起訴謀殺
He's gonna be charged with murder.
-保護他的安全  -為什麼  你要去哪裡
- Keep him safe. - Why? Where are you going?
我會把詳情簡訊告訴你  還有我們沒扯平
I'll text you the info. And this does not make us square.
但是做些
But doing something...
好事
good...
可以讓你不那麼討厭自己  相信我
it helps with the self-loathing. Trust me.
你知道  他是故意把這留在這裡讓你發現的
You know, he left this here for you to find.
真隱蔽啊  是不是
Subtle, right?
船停在哈德遜渡輪碼頭  我找到帳單了
It's docked at the Hudson Ferry Terminal. I found the bills.
他想讓你去那裡
And he wants you to go there.
他真有自信
He must be feeling confident.
至少這一切能結束了
At least now it'll end.
不管結果如何
One way or another.
乘客通道
終於迎來最後一輪了
And here we are for the last and final round.
不敢看著我的眼睛嗎
Too afraid to look me in the eye?
出來吧
Present arms.
以防萬一爸爸的藥沒效果
Just in case Dad's potion doesn't work.
傑西卡
Jessica.
我要求你把臉露出來
I demand that you show me your face-- -
上帝啊  是帕茜
Oh, for God's sake, it's Patsy!
開槍
Shoot her!
再見了  傑西卡
Goodbye, Jessica.
我就在後面
I'm right behind you.
上  上
Go, go!
難以置信
Unbelievable.
把遊艇準備好
Ready the yacht.
自相殘殺吧
Start killing each other.
動手
Now!
停下
Stop!
別侮辱我的智商  你在裝模作樣不是嗎
Don't insult my intelligence. You're faking, aren't you?
什麼裝模作樣
Faking what?
很明顯你有計劃
Obviously, you have a plan.
不然你就會跳過他們殺了我  所以
Otherwise, you'd have jumped over them all and I'd be dead, so...
說吧
do share.
我要你讓他們住手
I wanted you to make them stop.
胡扯  把我殺了不就行了
Bollocks, killing me would accomplish that, wouldn't it?
你從沒死過
You've never died before.
你總是一副英雄的樣子  是嗎
Always a sodding hero, aren't you?
不
No.
聰明的姑娘  聰明的姑娘
Clever girl. Clever, clever girl.
假裝順從我
Pretending to give me what I want.
雖然我也如此希望
I'd hoped for it.
上帝啊  真誘惑
God, it is so tempting...
相信這一切
to buy into this act.
我對你的期望根本無法實現
I've been asking the impossible of you.
我現在知道了
I see that now.
我想讓你愛我
I wanted you to love me.
但你從沒愛過任何人  你根本無法愛上誰
But you've never loved anyone. You're not even capable of it.
除了一個例外
With one exception.
過來  帕茜
Come here, Patsy.
你會不惜一切代價保護她  是嗎
You'd do anything to protect her, wouldn't you?
是的
Yes.
也許我選錯人了
Yeah, perhaps I chose the wrong sister.
你是不是覺得  我會每天強姦她
From your perspective, I'll be raping her every day.
每天和她肌膚相親
My skin will be touching hers.
她會變成我的玩物
She'll be my plaything.
我的奴隸
She'll be my slave.
而在她腦中  她與死無異  是嗎
And in her mind, she'll be dying, isn't that right?
是的
Yes.
我們走了
We're leaving.
如果你試圖找我們  如果我們看到你
If Patsy or I ever hear from you, or see you,
或者看到長得像你的人
see anyone who looks like you,
我就會讓她割喉自盡
she will slit her own throat.
這是最終防範措施
It's the ultimate contingency.
親我
Kiss me.
認真的
Mean it.
上帝啊  是真的  是嗎
Oh, God, it's true, isn't it?
你會讓我帶走你姐姐
You would let me take your beloved sister.
上帝啊
My God.
終於結束了  你是我的了
It's finally over. You're mine now.
不再有抗爭  不再有各種戲碼
No more fighting. No more of these ugly displays.
你是我的了
You'll be with me now.
聽著  隨著時間流逝
Look, after a while...
不管要多久  我知道
however long it takes... I know...
我知道你會和我有同樣的感覺
I know you will feel what I feel.
先笑一個吧
Let's start with a smile.
告訴我你愛我
Tell me you love me.
我愛你
I love you.
笑一個
Smile.
慢點
Go slow.
我是傑西卡的朋友
I'm a friend of Jessica's.
我怎麼會在這裡
How did I get here?
傑西卡
Jessica.
我也幫了點忙
Well, I helped.
她在哪裡
Where is she?
她被逮捕了
She's been arrested.
她殺了人  新聞上都在播
She killed someone. It's all over the news.
她
She...
-他找到她了  -不  不
- He got to her. - No, no, no.
是她找到他了
She got to him.
基爾格雷夫死了
Killgrave is dead.
她成功了
She did it.
是的  她成功了
Yeah, she did it.
她會因此進監獄的
They can lock her up for that.
-我不能坐視不管  -夠了  夠了
- I won't let that happen. - Okay. Okay, enough.
她救你  你救她  然後她又要再救你
She saves you, you save her, then she has to save you again.
而你們誰都不想被人救  是嗎
And neither one of you want to be saved, right?
警察  在找我
The police... they're looking for me.
但他們暫時還顧不上你
But you're the least of their worries.
我們把你從醫院弄出來之後  那地方瘋了
After we got you out of the hospital, the place went nuts.
然後在碼頭  又有不少人陷入狂亂
Then down on the docks, some people went batshit crazy,
包括警察
including the cops.
相信我  現在沒人在找你
Trust me, no one's looking for you.
沒人知道你的事
Nobody knows about you.
除了我
Except me.
你知道什麼
What do you know?
我知道如何保守秘密
I know how to keep a secret.
你知道  傑西卡
You know, Jessica...
她是個好朋友
she's a good friend to have.
她很堅韌  而在你看來
She's all tough and shit, but where you're concerned...
她還是很堅韌
She's still tough and shit.
沒錯
Yeah.
你們倆真是一類人
You're two of a kind.
有水嗎
I could use some water.
你應該感到高興
You know, that should make you happy.
有人那麼關心你
Somebody caring about you like that.
尤其是你也有同樣的感覺
Particularly if you feel the same way.
雖然這不關我的事
Not that it's any of my business, but...
但是
I don't know...
也許你們應該好好經營
this might be something you want to work through.
看看發展
See what's possible.
傑西卡·瓊斯也不想經歷這一切
Jessica Jones didn't ask for this.
並不是她去找的它
She didn't go looking for it.
而是怪物找上的她
This monster found her.
她親手殺了個人  傑瑞
She killed a man with her bare hands, Jeri.
這也不是和她有關的第一起謀殺了
And it's not the first death she's been linked to.
這一次我們有目擊證人
Now we have witnesses.
所有證人都會作證
All of whom will testify
是他強迫他們自相殘殺
that he forced them to try to kill each other.
他們不過是一幫在遊艇上喝多了的醉漢
They were a bunch of drunken brawlers off a booze cruise.
得了  薩曼莎
Come on, Samantha.
你肯定驗過他們血液裡的酒精含量了
You must have tested their blood alcohol levels.
聽聽這個
Try this one.
他們感染了有毒氣體
They were exposed to a toxic gas leak.
或是水有問題  或是潛意識廣告
Or there's something in the water, or subliminal advertising.
我有很多種解釋  我只是不願意相信而已
I had dozens of justifications, I just didn't want to believe it.
即使有更多人受傷  或是被殺
Even as more people were hurt... or killed.
你是在作證嗎  傑瑞
Are you testifying, Jeri?
不  不需要
No, no need.
我有足夠多的證詞可以讓陪審團相信
I will have more than enough testimony to convince a jury
這個人強迫傑西卡擰斷了他的脖子
that this man forced Jessica to snap his own neck.
這就是你的辯詞  他是自殺
That's your defense? He committed suicide?
內疚
Guilt.
那內疚難以忍受
The guilt was un... unbearable.
他不能承受由他造成的痛苦
He couldn't live with all the pain... that he had caused.
無論如何  傑西卡別無選擇
Either way, Jessica did not have a choice.
她是被強迫的
She was compelled against her will.
這個人同時也強迫了一個無辜女子
And this same man compelled an innocent young woman...
殺了她的父母
to kill her own parents.
如果我當時有這些證人
If I had these same witnesses,
霍普·施洛曼就不會死了
Hope Shlottman would be alive today.
證人證詞無法證明大腦控制的存在
Witness testimony won't prove the existence of mind control.
去跟那些向我的當事人開槍的警察說去吧
Tell that to the police officers who opened fire on my client.
我等不及讓他們出庭作證了
I can't wait to get them on the stand.
還有要補充的嗎  瓊斯女士
Anything to add, Ms. Jones?
有人說每個人出生時都是英雄
They say everyone's born a hero.
但如果你不反抗
But if you let it,
生活會將你逐漸轉變成惡魔
life will push you over the line until you're the villain.
謝謝
Thank you.
這是我的文件  如你所要求
這些東西還有很多
愛你的媽媽
問題是  你有時候並不知道自己的改變
Problem is, you don't always know that you've crossed that line.
你有十二條新的留言
You have 12 new messages.
你是那個在碼頭救下所有人的女孩嗎
Hey, are you the chick who saved all the people on the docks?
有人強迫我交房租  我想
I'm being strong-armed for rent money, and I thought--
已刪除
Deleted.
你好  瓊斯女士
Hi, uh, Ms. Jones.
我的男朋友對我  家暴
My boyfriend has gotten... abusive,
我不知道該找誰
and I don't know who to turn to.
-我沒有  -已刪除
- I don't have any-- - Deleted.
傑西卡·瓊斯嗎  我需要幫助
Jessica Jones? I need your help.
我弟弟欠一些人的錢  但是
My brother owes some people money, but--
救我
Help me!
我兒子跑了
My son ran away--
傑西卡  求你救救我
Jessica, you have to save me!
也許這個世界認為我是個英雄就夠了
Maybe it's enough that the world thinks I'm a hero.
也許如果我工作時間夠長夠辛苦
Maybe if I work long and hard...
也許我就能欺騙我自己
maybe I can fool myself.
假名調查事務所  有什麼可以幫你的
Alias Investigations. How can we help?